goodyeartires.com 2007-12-17

# Goodyear Tire U.S. || Privacy Policy

**Basic Confidentiality and Privacy Policy**

The Goodyear Tire & Rubber Company, hereafter "Goodyear", considers personal information, such as your name, postal and e-mail addresses or telephone number, to be private and confidential. Accordingly, the personal information you provide is stored in a secure location, is accessible only by designated staff or authorized agents, and with the exception of online tire registration information (see below), is used only to market our products or better serve our customers. Goodyear will not disclose any personal information to other organizations. 

**Information Collection**

When you browse a Goodyear web site, you do so anonymously. Personal information is not collected. Some areas of our web sites, however, may request that you voluntarily supply us with personal information, including your name, email address, etc., for purposes such as correspondence, site registration, making a purchase, or participating in online surveys. 

Goodyear may also retain electronic communications you send to our customer service representatives, webmaster or other associates. These may be shared only within Goodyear as a means to continually improve customer service.

Goodyear web sites track information about the visits to those sites. For example, statistics are compiled that show the daily number of visitors to a site, the daily requests received for particular files on a site, and what countries those requests come from. These aggregated statistics are used to customize our web site to better meet your needs and may also be provided to others, but the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information. 

Certain Goodyear sites may use "cookies" or "web beacons." A "cookie" is an element of data that a web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your system. Cookies allow us to better serve visitors to our website by offering a tailored experience. A "web beacon", also referred to as a spotlight tag or pixel tag, is used to recognize unique cookies and assists us in determining which advertisements bring users to a specific website. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. If you decline to accept the cookie, it will also disable the web beacon. With both cookies and web beacons, the information collected and used is anonymous and not personally identifiable. The information collected does not contain your name, address, telephone number, or email address.

**Information Use**

Goodyear may use the information users give us to, for example, provide a service, measure consumer interest in our various products and services or inform users about new products and programs. These offers may be based on information provided in surveys, information that may indicate purchasing preferences or email sent to a Goodyear site. 

Any lists used to send you product and service offers are developed and managed under strict conditions designed to safeguard the security and privacy of customer personal information. Goodyear will use reasonable effort to address all requests to remove names from any postal mail or email lists. 

**Online Tire Registration Information**

Any information provided by users in the online tire registration form will not be shared with any third party other than as provided by law, nor will it be used for any marketing purposes. Any information you provide in the online tire registration form is maintained in a separate tire registration database and is not used for any other purposes. 

**Disclosure**

Because Goodyear considers the individual information we maintain to be confidential, our policy is to disclose no personal information gathered online to third parties unless release is required by law or is pertinent to judicial or government investigations or proceedings or the personal information is required for Goodyear to provide requested services to users and visitors to the site. Goodyear does not sell or rent personal information to other organizations unless specifically disclosed at the point of collection. Goodyear does not share personal information with unauthorized parties. For example, Goodyear has authorized a company to transmit marketing emails on our behalf. That company is not permitted to use the personal information for any secondary purposes. 

**Other Web Sites**

Goodyear web sites may contain links to other sites, and we make every effort to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy. However, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by other sites. 

**Children**

Goodyear does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information (such as name, address and telephone number) from children under 13 years old through its web site. Goodyear will specifically instruct children under 13 not to submit such information to this web site. We do not currently allow children under 13 to register or participate in contests or promotions on the site. However, if the parent or guardian of a child under 13 believes that the child has provided us with personally identifiable information, the parent or guardian of that child should [contact us](http://www.goodyear.com/cgi-bin/mail_new/mailto.pl?to=Global%20Communications&template=/email/mailto.html) if they want this information deleted from our files. If Goodyear obtains knowledge that it has personally identifiable information about a child under 13 in retrievable form in its files, we will delete that information from our existing files. In addition, anyone under 18 years old should seek their parent’s or guardian’s permission prior to using or disclosing any personal information on this site. 

**Disclaimer**

By using a Goodyear site, you signify your assent to the Goodyear online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our sites. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. 

**Copyrights**
